Come on, we're shining, running, forever!
The sea is calling out, so ride the waves!
We're all together as one,
so let's sail in the sun!
All our dreams are never ending,
Heartbeat, we will be one! Go ahead!
Even though our hearts have
traveled different paths.
We are best friends.
Our freedom is our only compass.
That's pointing us along the
many roads that come together.
We will keep on running forward every day.
Go east, go west.
As long as we keep looking to the horizon.
We'll see everything all crystal clear.
We're all so thrilled that we
can't wait until the dawn arrives.
So we'll just bring the
sun ourselves to know.
If the winds blow, is waiting
where we should be going, go?
That's right, we're
shining, running forever!
All of our dreams will
merge into one piece.
No matter where we go,
we'll be fine and free.
Cause all our treasure is our strength.
Come on, we're shining, running forever!
The sea is coming out, so ride away!
We're all together as well, so
let's just stay with the sun!
All our dreams are never ending, so
let's wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up!
Heartbeat, we will be one, go hey!
My darkness will swallow the
world, just you wait and see!
You think I'll lose to you?
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
Roger's treasure belongs to me!
We'll ride non-stop and travel farther
than we've ever gone And then tomorrow we
will find suspense And then commence to
live out another day so intense
That's right, we're shining,
running forever Let's go along
with curiosity Our feelings lead
the way straight to a brand new day Into
another adventure Come on, we're shining,
running forever Open the map inside your
heart and see No matter where we end up,
our minds will never give up There's a
fire in our dreams and you can never,
never, never, never stop it
We will be one, go ahead!
The ring has completely capsized!
But somehow, the water
level is plunging with it!
We can no longer guarantee
the safety of our guests!
Please evacuate the Coliseum at once!
Don't choke me!
I'm slipping!
My strength!
Hey, wait!
We weren't actually planning
on giving that prize away!
Huh?
You're all out of bounds.
That makes me the victor.
Whoever nabs this thing wins, right?
He's got it!
Thanks for the prize.
We have a winner!
I know it seems trivial at the moment.
But in the thick of the chaos.
Our top dog has finally emerged.
The dark horse in the competition.
Has climbed to the top.
It's Lucy.
He is our champion.
Gross.
I can't fall out.
Much longer.
Sir, you think maybe you could
help me out, too? You're a pirate.
Pull yourself up by your own bootstraps.
Predictable, but so cool. Brace yourself.
I'm about to light things up. What?
Cheater!
That fruit was supposed to be mine!
Huh?
Isn't he from the Revolutionary Army?
God, that's hot.
It's really working.
Oh, I guess that's my cue.
Wait, it's not that hot, actually.
It's like I've become the fire.
Ace, I take your ability.
Fire!
Mr. Sam!
Damn you Straw Hats, who
do you think you are, huh?
That was cruel! Servants!
I won't let any of you leave
here alive, do you hear me?
Take Usopp and run!
Sure, Robin!
Let's go, then!
Don't let him lay a
goopy finger on Ozolin!
Let me take a wild guess.
You want to trash the factory?
Sound about right?
Niko Robin?
Stinky Stinky Chain!
Hold it! Huh?
Ah!
You little people, huh?
Mind if I borrow this guy for a second?
Ah! Ah!
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Hmm, he must have fought real hard
to save us if he's in this condition.
Everyone, look!
I heard that some of you for a
decade have been living as slaves.
It must have been hard.
If it weren't for you, we would have
lived out the rest of our days as toys.
Enslaved in this hellish nightmare, but
you allowed us to reclaim our identities.
Gaze your eyes upon this man.
Remember this face well as the
hero who shattered our curse!
Captain Usopp! Yeah!
We thank you!
Woo-hoo!
Huh?
What fell?
Did the ceiling topple?
He looks godly!
That aura! My god!
Don't tell me!
We've been saved by a real deity!
Then that means we're
Witnessing a miracle!
So saintly, so holy.
You
people will
be guided
by me?
You people will be guided by me.
So you really are
sent down from heaven.
We humbly bow down to you, great savior.
We will follow your command,
God Usopp! Anything!
Just tell us what to do!
Show us the way, mighty God Usopp!
What must we do?
Well,
uh, in that case,
why don't you all destroy the factory
behind me and rescue our little friends?
Gladly, great one! Yeah!
Uzzel, let's go!
What the hell?
I thought Lucy was Straw Hat.
I was supposed to be the one
to eat the flame flame fruit.
Just great.
Now how am I supposed to
break this noose to Dofie?
What do these goons want?
Get him!
He works for Doflamingo!
ANNIHILATOR!
AND THEN THE FACTORY!
I see.
So are these the TOR people?
Yikes.
Well, this is gonna be
something fun to get used to.
Hey, um...
Please don't take this as criticism,
but that was kinda messed up, sir!
I KNOW I CAN MAKE BARRIERS AND ALL, BUT
THAT DOESN'T MEAN THAT I'M INVINCIBLE.
UGH, NOT THAT GUY.
WHO ARE YOU?
COME OUT AND SAY IT ALREADY.
ME?
THE NAME IS SABO.
WE'RE MEMBERS OF THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY.
Then the first Lucy is two?
No, but we're both enemies
of the world government.
That man will be the king
of the pirates someday.
His name is Straw Hat Luffy.
A pirate?
Yep.
And he's my brother.
Surprised?
Crazy, huh?
And he's a hell of a guy.
He's still the same kid.
Reckless as hell.
That's funny, since I can
say the same thing about you.
Hey, now.
So wait, what brought you
guys to Drithrosa? Tell me.
Weapons?
This place is exporting firearms that are
contributing to wars around the world.
We're here to put a stop to that.
On several occasions,
the revolutionary army has sent
operatives to this kingdom;
however, since they were turned into toys,
none of them ever returned, which is why
we were unable to gather enough evidence.
That guy in blue's gonna be a problem.
Yeah, that's Sabo, right?
What's the number two of the
Revolutionary Army doing here?
We have to warn the crew!
It seems they're manufacturing
the weapons elsewhere, though.
Hmm.
But where?
Who's producing all these firearms?
if we can uncover the truth we'll have
something substantial to bring back to dragon
Yuffei!
How dare you kill the young master!
I'll blow you away!
Buffalo!
Trophy!
I'm here to save you! Straw Hat? Oh, good!
You didn't die!
I thought we agreed you'd
destroy the factory, Straw Hat.
Did you?
Or not?
Here's the keys to his handcuffs.
Wow, you're ready for anything, aren't ya?
Wait!
Straw Hat Violet!
I won't let you lay a finger on...
Young Master?
There, King Rick.
I'm sorry for the wait.
Just a sec.
I'm gonna get you out of here, okay?
Thanks, but I'll pass.
Our alliance from here
on out is terminated.
So get lost.
You're so selfish.
I want to keep working
with you, so deal with it.
Who's the selfish one now?
Hurry, use the key. Oh, right.
You do realize what the Alliance
called off were enemies?
If you set me free, I'll kill you!
That's it—this is hard enough to
unlock with this dumb sea prism stone!
So stop squirming, steady you two—aren't
paying attention to me at all?
Are you?
are you
He's the wall guy! Mingo!
What a way to go, huh?
That was a surprise.
Wait, Mingo is alive?
Young master! You're alive?
How is this possible?
The whole country should be spiraling into
chaos now that all the
toys have been freed.
And for whatever reason,
we have some members of the
Revolutionary Army nosing around, too.
I'm left in a difficult position.
I have no other choice
but to use the birdcage.
The birdcage?
You remember, don't you, Law?
Think we should book it?
They're on a rampage and
headed straight here!
This is above my pay grade!
Well, lucky for us.
I don't think that they can
actually reach us without the key.
You know, this factory means
everything to the young master.
Even if the ceiling collapses,
there won't be a scratch on this place
since it's made of sea prism stone.
Besides, need I remind you?
We've got two of the top
executives watching over it.
Trust me when I say no one
can get through these two.
Our impenetrable defenses
really are impenetrable!
Koala!
Robin!
I thought I recognized you back there.
Have you been well? Yeah!
Sabo! Hack!
You haven't changed a bit!
Hey!
Run into Luffy yet?
He... okay?
Mm-hmm.
This guy is one of our crewmates.
He's Usopp.
He should probably rest.
Doflamingo!
Pardon me, but I must hastily proceed.
I guess things are starting
to heat up down there.
I hope they don't need a hand.
Well, whatever.
I gotta find that rock guy.
What a pain.
Well, I suppose I shouldn't
delay this further.
Shut your damn mouth!
How can you still be alive, Doflamingo?
Do you want me to show you how to
properly behead a man? Soldier!
Kidos, behind you!
Just like this.
Kidos, no!
Damn Straw Hat!
There's two young masters?
Sorry, by mistake.
Hey, jerk, gump, gump!
Huh, armaments.
Jack Statlin!
Huh?
Lufin-Lan!
But how?
He has a double?
That hurt.
It seems he's made a
marionette out of his strength.
That technique, what is it?
Rick, a quick question.
Do you remember how you felt
that evening ten years ago?
The one where you torched the town and
sliced your beloved citizens to pieces?
Please, kill me!
I could never forget such a tragedy.
That nightmare haunts me to this day.
Compared to what's about to unfold,
that will seem like a sweet memory.
Hmm?
You're mad. What are you planning?
You cannot repeat such a callous act.
Hush now.
I'm going to release you all pika I
Think it's time you scatter these roaches
The Flamingo, you have done
enough damage to these people!
Don't put them through anymore!
Hang on, guys!
Gum-Gum!
Nooo! No!
He chucked us right out of the palace.
There's no chance of us getting
near Doflamingo if Pika is with him.
A birdcage.
It's starting.
Skye!
What's that, sir?
Who knows?
Let's not stay and find out!
We're no match for Doflamingo, so
there's no point in lashing out at him!
Captain, watch out! Something's there!
Why?
Huh? Razors?
Huh?
Are these bars always here?
Before the truth behind this regime
even has a chance to get out.
Doflamingo will kill
every person in Dressrosa.
This fence stretches as far as we can see.
What the hell?
Where's the exit?
What are these beams around us?
Vice Admiral Bastille, I
can't contact headquarters.
What? Same here.
I'm having technical
difficulties reaching the base.
How am I going to report
the events from today?
Hey!
Don't fire at someone's home!
I...
I didn't...
I can't control my own body!
Hey! Stop that!
My arm's moving on its own!
Stop me!
Everybody, stop!
Parasite String
Sir, reporting in.
It's pandemonium all across Dressrosa.
Everyone's going wild and
attacking one another.
I'm sad to inform you that there's even
submarines attacking the civilians.
We need backup or many
innocent people will die.
What's going on now?
The King's Plateau is sinking!
Hey!
Why is the ground shaky?
Who's doing this?
It's Pika.
He's changing the terrain
with his stone powers.
The royal palace is running away!
Stop!
You get back here!
Look out!
The factory is ascending! What?
How is that even possible?
Help me!
Please stop me!
Look at the flower field!
It's rising up!
And pulling the whole town with it!
Citizens and guests of
Dressrosa, greetings.
Might I have a word?
When I started my reign, I could have
easily ruled over you with an iron fist.
Instead, I was benevolent.
But now that you know the truth,
there's no doubt in my mind that the vast
majority of you would like to see me dead.
That's why I've prepared
a little game for you.
Your objective is to assassinate me.
You can find me in the royal palace.
I won't be going anywhere.
Take my life and the game ends.
I die, you win.
Real simple, right?
And since I'm so generous, I'll give
you a second way to win as well.
I'm about to read out a list of
people, so get your pencils ready.
Should you manage to bring me
their dead bodies, you win.
Also, I will award a sizable bounty
for each and every head I receive.
It's kill or be killed.
Every person in the kingdom
is now a bounty hunter.
And the only way for you to survive
is for you to take the
life of another person.